Wednesday	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Sheffield	comeback	Wednes	nesday	O
Wednesday	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	both	and	Wednes	nesday	O
McDonald	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	a	's	McDona	Donald	B-PER
's	POS	B-NP	I-ORG	0	1	0	McDonald	fast-food	's	's	O
Aviv	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Tel	(	Aviv	Aviv	I-LOC
Limoges	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	13	(	Limoge	imoges	B-LOC
Berlin	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Alba	(	Berlin	Berlin	B-LOC
Charleroi	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	14	(	Charle	rleroi	B-LOC
Ljubljana	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	16	(	Ljublj	bljana	B-LOC
Villeurbanne	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	15	(	Villeu	rbanne	B-LOC
Split	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	13	(	Split	Split	O
Pau-Orthez	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	16	(	Pau-Or	Orthez	B-PER
Kinder	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	14	Bologna	Kinder	Kinder	B-PER
All	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	plus	Black	All	All	O
Black	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	All	forwards	Black	Black	I-MISC
Galati	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Otelul	and	Galati	Galati	I-PER
REUTER	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	SOCCER	REUTER	REUTER	B-PER
Arab	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	:	Contractors	Arab	Arab	B-MISC
Contractors	NNS	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Arab	(	Contra	actors	O
League	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	Hockey	teams	League	League	I-MISC
HARTFORD	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	PTS	12	HARTFO	RTFORD	B-LOC
BUFFALO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	30	13	BUFFAL	UFFALO	B-LOC
BOSTON	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	27	10	BOSTON	BOSTON	B-LOC
OTTAWA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	21	7	OTTAWA	OTTAWA	B-LOC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	30	JERSEY	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
JERSEY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	NEW	14	JERSEY	JERSEY	I-LOC
WASHINGTON	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	29	13	WASHIN	INGTON	B-LOC
NY	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	25	ISLANDERS	NY	NY	B-LOC
TAMPA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	22	BAY	TAMPA	TAMPA	B-LOC
DALLAS	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	34	16	DALLAS	DALLAS	B-LOC
CHICAGO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	33	12	CHICAG	HICAGO	B-LOC
TORONTO	TO	B-VP	B-ORG	1	0	0	26	11	TORONT	ORONTO	B-LOC
PHOENIX	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	22	9	PHOENI	HOENIX	B-LOC
VANCOUVER	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	38	14	VANCOU	COUVER	B-LOC
EDMONTON	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	29	13	EDMONT	MONTON	B-LOC
SAN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	25	JOSE	SAN	SAN	B-LOC
JOSE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	SAN	10	JOSE	JOSE	I-LOC
CALGARY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	24	10	CALGAR	ALGARY	B-LOC
NY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	AT	RANGERS	NY	NY	B-LOC
League	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	Hockey	games	League	League	I-MISC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	2	JERSEY	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
EAGLES	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	CLOBBER	TO	EAGLES	EAGLES	O
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	York	New	New	B-LOC
Arizona	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	entertain	.	Arizon	rizona	B-LOC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	-	YORK	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	NEW	10	YORK	YORK	I-LOC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	9	JERSEY	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
UTAH	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	-	14	UTAH	UTAH	B-LOC
DALLAS	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	1/2	6	DALLAS	DALLAS	B-LOC
SAN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1/2	ANTONIO	SAN	SAN	B-LOC
VANCOUVER	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	12	2	VANCOU	COUVER	B-LOC
LAKERS	NNS	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	LA	13	LAKERS	LAKERS	O
GOLDEN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	7	STATE	GOLDEN	GOLDEN	O
STATE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	GOLDEN	6	STATE	STATE	O
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	6	JERSEY	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
JERSEY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	NEW	AT	JERSEY	JERSEY	I-LOC
League	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Football	standings	League	League	I-MISC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	PA	ENGLAND	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
ENGLAND	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	NEW	9	ENGLAN	NGLAND	B-LOC
BUFFALO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	269	9	BUFFAL	UFFALO	B-LOC
MIAMI	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	284	6	MIAMI	MIAMI	B-LOC
JACKSONVILLE	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	254	6	JACKSO	NVILLE	B-LOC
SAN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	230	DIEGO	SAN	SAN	B-LOC
WASHINGTON	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	201	8	WASHIN	INGTON	B-LOC
NY	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	332	GIANTS	NY	NY	B-LOC
TAMPA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	289	BAY	TAMPA	TAMPA	B-LOC
NEW	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	393	ORLEANS	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
NY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	ARIZONA	JETS	NY	NY	O
JETS	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	NY	AT	JETS	JETS	B-MISC
INDIANAPOLIS	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	:	37	INDIAN	APOLIS	B-LOC
Philadelphia	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	37	10	Philad	elphia	B-LOC
NCAA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	10	AMERICAN	NCAA	NCAA	B-MISC
Ohio	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-05	State	Ohio	Ohio	B-LOC
State	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Ohio	left	State	State	O
Ohio	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	helped	State	Ohio	Ohio	B-LOC
State	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Arizona	.	State	State	O
State	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Arizona	offensive	State	State	O
Nebraska	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	of	.	Nebras	braska	B-LOC
Green	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Bay	Green	Green	B-LOC
1.	CD	B-NP	B-ORG	0	0	1	27	FC	1.	1.	O
04	CD	I-NP	I-ORG	0	1	0	Schalke	17	04	04	O
Munich	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	1860	17	Munich	Munich	B-LOC
Paris	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	St	Paris	Paris	B-LOC
Oviedo	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	,	Oviedo	Oviedo	B-LOC
Salamanca	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	,	Salama	amanca	B-LOC
REAL	NNP	O	B-ORG	1	1	1	ON	MADRID	REAL	REAL	O
Valencia	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	20	15	Valenc	lencia	B-LOC
Oviedo	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	16	15	Oviedo	Oviedo	B-LOC
Logrones	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	16	15	Logron	grones	O
Compostela	RB	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	14	15	Compos	ostela	B-LOC
dello	DT	I-NP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Gazzetta	Sport	dello	dello	O
Milan	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	during	's	Milan	Milan	B-LOC
MANCHESTER	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	TWO	UNITED	MANCHE	HESTER	B-LOC
Vicenza	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	leaders	,	Vicenz	icenza	B-LOC
Napoli	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	In-form	should	Napoli	Napoli	I-PER
Verona	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	's	Verona	Verona	B-LOC
Vicenza	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	(	Vicenz	icenza	B-LOC
Vicenza	NN	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	strength	,	Vicenz	icenza	B-LOC
Charleroi	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	:	(	Charle	rleroi	B-LOC
Charleroi	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	:	-	Charle	rleroi	B-LOC
Kinder	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	78	Bologna	Kinder	Kinder	B-PER
Dnes	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Fronta	that	Dnes	Dnes	I-PER
RADIO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	ROMANIA	RADIO	RADIO	O
ROMANIA	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	RADIO	AFTERNOON	ROMANI	OMANIA	B-LOC
Social	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Democratic	Social	Social	O
Hungarian	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Democratic	Hungar	garian	B-MISC
Czech	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	ruling	Civic	Czech	Czech	B-MISC
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	powerful	Senate	U.S.	U.S.	B-LOC
Democrats	NNPS	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Radical	(	Democr	ocrats	B-MISC
Zywiec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	year	,	Zywiec	Zywiec	B-MISC
w	IN	I-NP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Piwowarskie	Zywcu	w	w	O
Zywiec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	is	Zywiec	Zywiec	B-LOC
Okocim	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	in	.	Okocim	Okocim	B-LOC
South	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	year	African	South	South	B-MISC
Tychy	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	brewers	Tychy	Tychy	B-LOC
EB	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	EB	EB	B-LOC
Zywiec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	prevented	from	Zywiec	Zywiec	B-PER
CEFTA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	for	countries	CEFTA	CEFTA	B-LOC
Zywiec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	said	had	Zywiec	Zywiec	B-PER
Zywiec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	that	's	Zywiec	Zywiec	B-LOC
Zywiec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	,	Full	Zywiec	Zywiec	B-LOC
Zywiec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	said	would	Zywiec	Zywiec	B-PER
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Department	Transport	of	of	O
Tambang	VBG	B-VP	B-ORG	1	0	1	"	Timah	Tamban	ambang	O
PT	PRP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-07	Tambang	PT	PT	O
Tambang	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	PT	Timah	Tamban	ambang	O
PT	PRP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-07	Telekomunikasi	PT	PT	O
Indonesia	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Telekomunikasi	(	Indone	onesia	B-LOC
Irish	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	three	Republican	Irish	Irish	B-MISC
Army	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Republican	mortar	Army	Army	O
Trade	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	and	Trade	Trade	O
and	CC	I-NP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Trade	Industry	and	and	O
Industry	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	1	and	Secretary	Indust	dustry	O
Trading	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Fair	,	Tradin	rading	I-MISC
BA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	where	and	BA	BA	B-LOC
AA	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	currently	AA	AA	O
American	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	drop	Americ	erican	B-MISC
American	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	's	Americ	erican	B-MISC
American	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	should	Americ	erican	B-MISC
American	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	/	to	Americ	erican	B-MISC
Office	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	the	of	Office	Office	B-MISC
Trading	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Fair	by	Tradin	rading	I-MISC
Sale	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	attended	Grammar	Sale	Sale	O
Grammar	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Sale	School	Gramma	rammar	I-MISC
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	House	Commons	of	of	O
Commons	NNPS	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	lower	Common	ommons	B-LOC
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	House	Commons	of	of	O
Commons	NNPS	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	or	Common	ommons	O
Manitoba	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	:	Government	Manito	nitoba	B-LOC
Manitoba	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	87.16	's	Manito	nitoba	B-LOC
Canadian	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	The	Wheat	Canadi	nadian	B-MISC
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	--	York	New	New	B-LOC
China	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	30,000	Steel	China	China	B-LOC
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	--	York	New	New	B-LOC
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	--	York	New	New	B-LOC
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	--	York	New	New	B-LOC
,	,	O	I-ORG	0	1	1	Goldman	Sachs	,	,	O
Sachs	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	,	,	Sachs	Sachs	B-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	for	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	if	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	rejects	Fe	Fe	I-LOC
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	is	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	and	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	would	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	predict	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	will	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	deal	Fe	Fe	I-LOC
Santa	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	acquisition	Fe	Fe	I-LOC
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	as	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	saviors	Fe	Fe	I-LOC
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	match	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	's	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	is	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	has	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	with	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	,	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Homestake	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	think	could	Homest	estake	O
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	(	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	)	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	each	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	shares	Fe	Fe	I-LOC
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	Friday	York	New	New	B-LOC
Newmonth	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	,	was	Newmon	wmonth	B-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	while	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	added	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	with	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-MISC
Fe	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	,	Fe	Fe	I-PER
Santa	VB	I-VP	B-ORG	1	0	1	to	Fe	Santa	Santa	B-PER
Fe	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Santa	's	Fe	Fe	I-LOC
Wall	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	--	Street	Wall	Wall	B-LOC
Street	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Wall	Desk	Street	Street	I-LOC
Russ	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Berrie	Russ	Russ	B-PER
Berrie	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Russ	president	Berrie	Berrie	I-PER
Russ	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-06	Berrie	Russ	Russ	B-PER
Berrie	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Russ	and	Berrie	Berrie	I-PER
and	CC	O	I-ORG	0	1	1	Berrie	Co	and	and	O
Medecins	NNPS	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	charity	sans	Medeci	decins	B-PER
sans	FW	I-NP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Medecins	Frontieres	sans	sans	O
Russian	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Weather	Russia	ussian	B-MISC
Democratic	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Left	Democr	cratic	B-MISC
Church	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Catholic	too	Church	Church	I-LOC
Plus	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Rinaco	and	Plus	Plus	O
Norilsky	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	RAO	Nikel	Norils	rilsky	I-PER
Nikel	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Norilsky	0#NKEL.RUO	Nikel	Nikel	I-PER
United	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	at	City	United	United	B-LOC
Interrosimpex	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	through	in	Interr	simpex	B-PER
Uneximbank	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	"	has	Unexim	imbank	O
Pank	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Tallinna	11-mo	Pank	Pank	I-PER
Tallinna	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-06	Pank	Tallin	llinna	B-LOC
Pank	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Tallinna	,	Pank	Pank	I-PER
Tallinna	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Pank	Tallin	llinna	B-LOC
Pank	NNPS	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Tallinna	said	Pank	Pank	I-PER
for	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	0	Movement	a	for	for	O
a	DT	B-NP	I-ORG	0	0	1	for	Democratic	a	a	O
Democratic	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	1	a	Slovakia	Democr	cratic	B-MISC
Sidek	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	debt-ridden	group	Sidek	Sidek	B-PER
Sidek	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	fell	Sidek	Sidek	B-PER
Brazilian	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Plastic	Brazil	zilian	B-MISC
Society	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Surgery	(	Societ	ociety	O
SBCP	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	SBCP	SBCP	B-PER
SBCP	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	"	Vice-President	SBCP	SBCP	B-PER
Buenos	NNPS	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	--	Aires	Buenos	Buenos	B-LOC
Finance	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	,	Minister	Financ	inance	O
the	DT	B-NP	I-ORG	0	0	1	of	Islamic	the	the	O
Islamic	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	1	the	Conference	Islami	slamic	B-MISC
(	(	O	I-ORG	0	1	1	Ranyon	Rangoon	(	(	O
Rangoon	NN	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	Rangoo	angoon	B-LOC
)	)	O	I-ORG	0	1	1	Rangoon	University	)	)	O
University	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	)	early	Univer	ersity	O
Rangoon	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	from	University	Rangoo	angoon	B-LOC
Yangon	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	troubled	Institute	Yangon	Yangon	B-LOC
Technology	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	in	Techno	nology	O
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	University	Yangon	of	of	O
Yangon	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	six	Yangon	Yangon	B-LOC
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	University	Yangon	of	of	O
Yangon	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	from	Yangon	Yangon	B-LOC
National	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	's	League	Nation	tional	B-MISC
League	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	National	for	League	League	I-MISC
ICFTU	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	an	conference	ICFTU	ICFTU	O
Southeast	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	1	of	Asian	Southe	theast	B-MISC
Asian	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Southeast	Nations	Asian	Asian	I-MISC
Nations	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Asian	(	Nation	ations	I-MISC
ILO	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	the	agenda	ILO	ILO	O
ASEAN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	groups	ASEAN	ASEAN	B-LOC
ICFTU	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	to	delegates	ICFTU	ICFTU	O
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Board	India	of	of	O
India	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	said	India	India	B-LOC
Japan	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	(	Japan	Japan	B-LOC
Union	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	at	Bank	Union	Union	B-LOC
Switzerland	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	in	Switze	erland	B-LOC
Toyo	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	at	Trust	Toyo	Toyo	B-LOC
Haitham	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Haddadin	Haitha	aitham	B-PER
Haddadin	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Haitham	BEIRUT	Haddad	ddadin	I-PER
South	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Lebanon	South	South	B-LOC
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	0	Guardians	the	of	of	I-MISC
the	DT	B-NP	I-ORG	0	0	1	of	Cedars	the	the	O
MOODY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	BONDS	'S	MOODY	MOODY	O
State	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	11,880M	Street	State	State	O
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	Circuit	Court	U.S.	U.S.	B-LOC
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	--	York	New	New	B-LOC
Reuter	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	Reuter	Reuter	B-PER
Canadian	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	-	Grain	Canadi	nadian	B-MISC
NYMEX	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	)	natgas	NYMEX	NYMEX	O
NYMEX	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-06	Henry	NYMEX	NYMEX	O
NYMEX	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	said	NYMEX	NYMEX	O
AECO	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	the	storage	AECO	AECO	O
NYMEX	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Permian	NYMEX	NYMEX	O
NYMEX	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	premium	NYMEX	NYMEX	O
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	,	York	New	New	B-LOC
CBOT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	8720	grain	CBOT	CBOT	O
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Board	Trade	of	of	O
Trade	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	-	Trade	Trade	O
Motorsport	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	acquire	Traditions	Motors	rsport	B-MISC
Animal	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Glencoe	Hospital	Animal	Animal	I-LOC
Hospital	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Animal	in	Hospit	spital	I-LOC
American	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Veterinary	Americ	erican	B-MISC
the	DT	B-NP	I-ORG	0	0	1	of	Islamic	the	the	O
Islamic	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	1	the	Conference	Islami	slamic	B-MISC
General	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	185-members	Assembly	Genera	eneral	O
Herri	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	by	Batasuna	Herri	Herri	B-PER
Batasuna	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Herri	,	Batasu	tasuna	I-PER
AN	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	AN	AN	O
AN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	after	leader	AN	AN	O
AN	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	,	's	AN	AN	O
Chamber	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	the	of	Chambe	hamber	O
Deputies	NNPS	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	(	Deputi	puties	O
AN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	accused	leaders	AN	AN	O
Chamber	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	the	,	Chambe	hamber	O
AN	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	quitting	's	AN	AN	O
MS-Fiamma	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	MS-Fia	Fiamma	B-PER
BJP	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	,	deputies	BJP	BJP	B-LOC
China	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	shinc	Steel	China	China	B-LOC
Coe	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	shinc	and	Coe	Coe	B-PER
and	CC	I-NP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Coe	Clerici	and	and	O
Clerici	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	and	.	Cleric	lerici	B-PER
China	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	shinc	Steel	China	China	B-LOC
NYMEX	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	,	crude	NYMEX	NYMEX	O
NYMEX	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	gasoline	NYMEX	NYMEX	O
FBI	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	Three	agents	FBI	FBI	B-MISC
X	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Pius	High	X	X	I-MISC
High	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	X	School	High	High	O
School	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	High	in	School	School	O
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Mexico	New	New	B-LOC
Mexico	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	New	Activities	Mexico	Mexico	I-LOC
America	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	,	Americ	merica	B-LOC
League	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Northern	on	League	League	I-MISC
Wednesday	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	next	.	Wednes	nesday	O
Antwerp	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	of	said	Antwer	ntwerp	B-LOC
Antwerp	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	to	from	Antwer	ntwerp	B-LOC
Munich	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	as	Re	Munich	Munich	B-MISC
Bundesbank	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	no	intervention	Bundes	esbank	B-MISC
John	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	Lewis	John	John	B-PER
Lewis	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	John	UK	Lewis	Lewis	I-PER
UK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Lewis	store	UK	UK	B-LOC
PT	PRP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-06	Tambang	PT	PT	O
Tambang	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	PT	Timah	Tamban	ambang	O
Cabinet	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	split	.	Cabine	abinet	O
Affairs	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Foreign	Minister	Affair	ffairs	O
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	South	New	New	B-LOC
South	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	New	Wales	South	South	I-LOC
Wales	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	South	Supreme	Wales	Wales	I-LOC
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	nationalist	Zealand	New	New	B-LOC
Zealand	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	New	First	Zealan	ealand	I-LOC
National	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	said	and	Nation	tional	O
NZ	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	and	First	NZ	NZ	B-LOC
First	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	NZ	would	First	First	O
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1996-12-06	Zealand	New	New	B-LOC
Zealand	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	New	First	Zealan	ealand	I-LOC
First	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Zealand	leader	First	First	O
NZ	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	between	First	NZ	NZ	B-LOC
First	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	NZ	and	First	First	O
National	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	negotiators	Nation	tional	O
National	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	had	Nation	tional	O
Technology	NN	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	(	Techno	nology	O
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	University	Yangon	of	of	O
Yangon	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	about	Yangon	Yangon	B-LOC
Wen	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Hui	Wen	Wen	B-PER
Bao	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Hui	newspaper	Bao	Bao	I-PER
Heavy	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Hyundai	pushed	Heavy	Heavy	O
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Administration	China	of	of	O
China	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	,	China	China	B-LOC
General	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	the	Administration	Genera	eneral	O
Customs	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	and	Custom	ustoms	O
Sangetsu	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	-	Sanget	ngetsu	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	,	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	both	and	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-MISC
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	said	and	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Mines	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	with	and	Mines	Mines	O
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	said	had	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	by	to	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	"	is	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	said	would	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	between	and	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-LOC
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	has	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	for	and	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	advised	to	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	both	and	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-MISC
Busang	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	the	gold	Busang	Busang	O
Bre-X	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	has	Bre-X	Bre-X	B-PER
I.D.E.A	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	house	.	I.D.E.	.D.E.A	I-PER
ISEAS	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	ISEAS	ISEAS	B-PER
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	0	1	1	University	Singapore	of	of	O
Singapore	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	.	Singap	gapore	B-LOC
NTT	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	in	's	NTT	NTT	B-LOC
PGA	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	the	and	PGA	PGA	B-MISC
III	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	USA	TO	III	III	O
USA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	piloted	III	USA	USA	B-LOC
Canada	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	I	Canada	Canada	B-LOC
I	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Canada	,	I	I	O
USA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	of	I	USA	USA	B-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	USA	's	I	I	O
United	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1.	States	United	United	B-LOC
States	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	United	III	States	States	I-LOC
Italy	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	2.	I	Italy	Italy	B-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Italy	(	I	I	O
Canada	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	3.	I	Canada	Canada	B-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Canada	(	I	I	O
German	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	4.	I	German	German	B-MISC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	German	(	I	I	O
Switzerland	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	5.	I	Switze	erland	B-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Switzerland	(	I	I	O
Germany	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	6.	III	German	ermany	B-LOC
III	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Germany	(	III	III	I-PER
Czech	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	7.	Republic	Czech	Czech	B-LOC
Republic	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	Czech	I	Republ	public	I-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Republic	(	I	I	O
Austria	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	8.	I	Austri	ustria	B-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Austria	(	I	I	O
Britain	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	9.	I	Britai	ritain	B-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Britain	(	I	I	O
United	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	.	States	United	United	B-LOC
States	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	United	I	States	States	I-LOC
I	PRP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	States	(	I	I	O
Austria	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	and	III	Austri	ustria	B-LOC
Chelsea	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	(	)	Chelse	helsea	B-PER
Gloucester	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	20	29	Glouce	cester	B-LOC
London	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	29	Irish	London	London	B-LOC
Irish	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	London	19	Irish	Irish	B-MISC
West	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	22	Hartlepool	West	West	B-LOC
Hartlepool	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	West	15	Hartle	lepool	I-LOC
Bristol	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	15	13	Bristo	ristol	B-LOC
Cardiff	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	20	34	Cardif	ardiff	B-LOC
Newport	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	10	45	Newpor	ewport	B-LOC
Watsonians	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	31	35	Watson	onians	B-PER
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	for	South	New	New	B-LOC
South	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	New	Wales	South	South	I-LOC
Wales	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	South	in	Wales	Wales	I-LOC
Wallaby	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	Former	captain	Wallab	allaby	O
Wednesday	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Sheffield	1	Wednes	nesday	O
Stirling	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	14	16	Stirli	irling	B-PER
East	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	12	Fife	East	East	B-LOC
Fife	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	East	14	Fife	Fife	I-LOC
Hamilton	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	34	15	Hamilt	milton	B-PER
Clyde	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	31	15	Clyde	Clyde	B-PER
Queen	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	22	of	Queen	Queen	O
South	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	of	16	South	South	B-LOC
Montrose	VB	B-VP	B-ORG	1	1	0	Three	17	Montro	ntrose	B-MISC
Ross	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	29	County	Ross	Ross	B-PER
Queen	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	22	's	Queen	Queen	O
's	POS	B-NP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Queen	Park	's	's	O
Park	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	0	's	16	Park	Park	B-LOC
Wimbledon	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	35	16	Wimble	bledon	B-MISC
Chelsea	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	26	16	Chelse	helsea	B-PER
Wednesday	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Sheffield	16	Wednes	nesday	O
Leicester	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	22	17	Leices	cester	B-LOC
West	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	17	Ham	West	West	B-LOC
Ham	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	West	16	Ham	Ham	I-LOC
Forest	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Nottingham	15	Forest	Forest	I-LOC
Birmingham	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	32	22	Birmin	ingham	B-LOC
West	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	26	Bromwich	West	West	B-PER
Chesterfield	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	37	21	Cheste	rfield	B-LOC
City	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Bristol	21	City	City	I-LOC
York	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	27	21	York	York	B-LOC
Preston	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	25	22	Presto	reston	B-PER
Cambridge	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	48	22	Cambri	bridge	B-LOC
Cardiff	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	40	21	Cardif	ardiff	B-LOC
Lincoln	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	30	22	Lincol	incoln	B-PER
Chester	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	30	21	Cheste	hester	B-LOC
Mansfield	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	24	21	Mansfi	sfield	B-PER
Brighton	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	22	22	Bright	ighton	B-LOC
ARSENAL	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	SAVES	WITH	ARSENA	RSENAL	O
Wednesday	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Sheffield	.	Wednes	nesday	O
Wimbledon	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	.	leap-frogged	Wimble	bledon	B-MISC
Wimbledon	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	for	,	Wimble	bledon	B-MISC
East	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	,	Fife	East	East	B-LOC
's	POS	B-NP	I-ORG	0	1	1	Queen	Park	's	's	O
Park	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	0	1	's	Scottish	Park	Park	O
Wednesday	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Sheffield	1	Wednes	nesday	O
West	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	:	Bromwich	West	West	B-PER
Boreham	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	2	Wood	Boreha	oreham	B-PER
Wood	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Boreham	1	Wood	Wood	I-PER
Town	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Ashford	0	Town	Town	I-LOC
BARBARIANS	VBZ	B-VP	B-ORG	1	1	0	BEAT	39-12	BARBAR	ARIANS	O
Albanian	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	of	Football	Albani	banian	B-MISC
Tasmania	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	against	on	Tasman	smania	B-LOC
Tasmania	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	between	and	Tasman	smania	B-LOC
Victoria	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	and	at	Victor	ctoria	B-LOC
Tasmania	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	:	481	Tasman	smania	B-LOC
Victoria	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	;	220	Victor	ctoria	B-LOC
Tikva	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Petah	12	Tikva	Tikva	I-LOC
Aviv	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Tel	12	Aviv	Aviv	I-LOC
Tikva	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Petah	12	Tikva	Tikva	I-LOC
Holon	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Zafririm	12	Holon	Holon	B-LOC
Aviv	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Tel	12	Aviv	Aviv	I-LOC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	-	YORK	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	NEW	11	YORK	YORK	I-LOC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	6	JERSEY	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
CLEVELAND	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	1/2	11	CLEVEL	VELAND	B-LOC
ATLANTA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	1/2	10	ATLANT	TLANTA	B-LOC
UTAH	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	-	15	UTAH	UTAH	B-LOC
SAN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	1/2	ANTONIO	SAN	SAN	B-LOC
VANCOUVER	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	1/2	3	VANCOU	COUVER	B-LOC
LAKERS	NNS	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	LA	14	LAKERS	LAKERS	O
PORTLAND	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	1/2	12	PORTLA	RTLAND	B-LOC
GOLDEN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	7	STATE	GOLDEN	GOLDEN	O
STATE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	GOLDEN	6	STATE	STATE	O
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	:	Jersey	New	New	B-LOC
Jersey	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	New	110	Jersey	Jersey	I-LOC
BOSTON	NN	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	110	108	BOSTON	BOSTON	B-LOC
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	81	York	New	New	B-LOC
York	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	New	103	York	York	I-LOC
MIAMI	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	103	85	MIAMI	MIAMI	B-LOC
Phoenix	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	85	101	Phoeni	hoenix	B-LOC
SACRAMENTO	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	101	95	SACRAM	AMENTO	B-LOC
Vancouver	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	95	105	Vancou	couver	B-LOC
SAN	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	105	ANTONIO	SAN	SAN	B-LOC
ANTONIO	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	SAN	89	ANTONI	NTONIO	I-LOC
UTAH	NNP	B-INTJ	B-ORG	1	0	0	89	106	UTAH	UTAH	B-LOC
Minnesota	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	106	95	Minnes	nesota	B-LOC
PORTLAND	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	95	97	PORTLA	RTLAND	B-LOC
Indiana	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	93	86	Indian	ndiana	B-LOC
GOLDEN	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	86	STATE	GOLDEN	GOLDEN	B-LOC
STATE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	GOLDEN	71	STATE	STATE	O
LAKERS	NNS	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	LA	92	LAKERS	LAKERS	O
Orlando	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	92	81	Orland	rlando	B-PER
League	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	Hockey	teams	League	League	I-MISC
HARTFORD	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	PTS	12	HARTFO	RTFORD	B-LOC
BUFFALO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	30	13	BUFFAL	UFFALO	B-LOC
BOSTON	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	26	10	BOSTON	BOSTON	B-LOC
OTTAWA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	23	7	OTTAWA	OTTAWA	B-LOC
NEW	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	32	JERSEY	NEW	NEW	B-LOC
JERSEY	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	NEW	14	JERSEY	JERSEY	I-LOC
WASHINGTON	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	29	13	WASHIN	INGTON	B-LOC
NY	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	27	ISLANDERS	NY	NY	B-LOC
TAMPA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	22	BAY	TAMPA	TAMPA	B-LOC
DALLAS	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	34	16	DALLAS	DALLAS	B-LOC
CHICAGO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	28	12	CHICAG	HICAGO	B-LOC
TORONTO	TO	B-VP	B-ORG	1	0	0	27	11	TORONT	ORONTO	B-LOC
PHOENIX	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	22	9	PHOENI	HOENIX	B-LOC
VANCOUVER	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	38	14	VANCOU	COUVER	B-LOC
EDMONTON	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	29	14	EDMONT	MONTON	B-LOC
SAN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	25	JOSE	SAN	SAN	B-LOC
JOSE	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	SAN	10	JOSE	JOSE	I-LOC
CALGARY	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	23	10	CALGAR	ALGARY	B-LOC
WASHINGTON	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	HARTFORD	AT	WASHIN	INGTON	B-LOC
OTTAWA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	JOSE	AT	OTTAWA	OTTAWA	B-LOC
League	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	Hockey	games	League	League	I-MISC
League	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	0	Hockey	and	League	League	I-MISC
Vancouver	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	by	after	Vancou	couver	B-LOC
Buffalo	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	in	zone	Buffal	uffalo	B-LOC
NHL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	said	discipline	NHL	NHL	B-MISC
Ottawa	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	against	.	Ottawa	Ottawa	B-LOC
IBF	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	IN	HEAVYWEIGHT	IBF	IBF	B-MISC
REAL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	1	0	FOR	.	REAL	REAL	O
Real	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	leaves	on	Real	Real	B-MISC
VOLENDAM	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	1	1	1	HIT	FOR	VOLEND	LENDAM	O
De	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	to	Graafschap	De	De	B-PER
Graafschap	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	1	1	1	De	Doetinchem	Graafs	fschap	I-PER
The	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	1	"	Super	The	The	O
Valencia	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	20	15	Valenc	lencia	B-LOC
Oviedo	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	16	15	Oviedo	Oviedo	B-LOC
Logrones	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	16	15	Logron	grones	O
Compostela	RB	B-NP	B-ORG	1	0	0	14	15	Compos	ostela	B-LOC
